This video is a derivative work of the original video.
Any resemblance to actual people, living or dead, is coincidental and unintentional.
I've been using AMD for 15 years.
I think the most common function I use is the basic version function, the line function,
and some of the big head needles, and some of the internal lines.
They are the most basic functions, but I've been using GPUs and rematches more recently.
When I first got in touch with AMD, I was quite surprised,
because it can quickly let me put the clothing pattern I need,
the clothing style, the clothing design,
and I can quickly make it.
Currently, I like the GPU operation function in AMD the most.
Now GPU operation is very good at solving the previous CPU operation pain points.
I've been using AMD for about seven or eight years.
I think AMD is very useful in game development.
It can shorten the time it takes to make high-end models,
and it can be calculated very quickly.
It can liberate designers' inspiration in design.
I've been using AMD for about four years.
My favorite function of AMD is the flexibility of the fabric.
It allows the fabric to be flexible.
It's hard to achieve in other 3D software,
but in AMD, it can imitate some hammering effects.
I've been using AMD for about nine years.
I work in the field of real-time decision-making assets.
I use AMD to solve all my materials.
My favorite function of AMD is the function of calculation.
When I use the function of calculation,
I will do a simulation of real-time materials.
The other function is that it can support a function called more target.
It feels very interesting.
When I first used AMD, I felt that this software was very convenient.
I can do things very quickly.
I can see the results very quickly.
It has a fan function.
It feels very fun.
I can blow my clothes up.
AMD has made a great improvement in efficiency for my work.
It is efficient and fast.
It helps us get more exquisite and realistic art effects.
The new version of AMD has improved its calculation speed
a lot compared to the previous one.
This is a great experience,
participating in this user summit.
I have seen lots of presentations and user stories.
User cases.
I came up with lots of ideas
on how to improve the software from their stories.
Marvelous Designers!